question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "category": "Science: Mathematics",
     "question": "Zero factorial is equal to zero. ",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science: Mathematics",
     "question": "An equilateral triangle always has every angle measuring 60&deg;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science: Mathematics",
     "question": "A scalene triangle has two sides of equal length.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science: Mathematics",
     "question": "A &#039;Millinillion&#039; is a real number.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science: Mathematics",
     "question": "The Pythagorean theorem states that the square of the"
                 " hypotenuse is equal to the product of the squares of the other two sides.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science: Mathematics",
     "question": "The proof for the Chinese Remainder Theorem used in Number Theory was"
                 " NOT developed by its first publisher, Sun Tzu.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Science: Mathematics",
     "question": "L&#039;H&ocirc;pital was the mathematician who created the homonymous rule that uses derivatives "
                 "to evaluate limits with indeterminations.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science: Mathematics",
     "question": "111,111,111 x 111,111,111 = 12,345,678,987,654,321",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science: Mathematics",
     "question": "The sum of any two odd integers is odd.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science: Mathematics",
     "question": "An isosceles triangle has two sides of equal length as opposed to three.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": [
         "False"]}]
